// questions.js
const questions = [
  {
    question: 'Who painted the Mona Lisa? (full name)',
    answer: 'Leonardo DiCaprio',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the speed of sound squared?',
    answer: 'loud',
  },
  {
    question: '1 + 1 = ?',
    answer: 'window',
  },
  {
    question: 'Roll a D20',
    answer: '7',
  },
  {
    question: 'Roll a D20',
    answer: '18',
  },
  {
    question: 'Roll a D20',
    answer: '2',
  },
  {
    question: 'True or False: There is a hole in your heart that you couldn\'t live without',
    answer: 'true',
  },
  {
    question: 'Name a five-headed dragon from "Yugioh"',
    answer: 'five headed dragon',
  },
  {
    question: 'What country could be a response to these two questions: "How are you feeling?", and "What kind of car do you drive?"',
    answer: 'Madagascar',
  },
  {
    question: 'John has 10 candles, each of which can burn for 10 minutes. John lights all of his candles. How many minutes do the candles burn in total?',
    answer: '100',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the laziest organ in the human body?',
    answer: 'brain',
  },
  {
    question: 'This country\'s leader is famous for having the worlds smallest male genitalia.',
    answer: 'Russia',
  },
  {
    question: 'Whenever A is true, B is always false. If A is false, what do we know about B?',
    answer: 'Nothing',
  },
  {
    question: 'A father gives his first son a quarter and his second son a nickel. What time is it?',
    answer: '6:51 PST',
  },
  {
    question: 'Within 10 decimal points, how many solar luminosities is the Sun?',
    answer: '1',
  },
  {
    question: 'More than 75% of the Earth\'s surface is covered in this.',
    answer: 'Air',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is a bird?',
    answer: 'a bird',
  },
  {
    question: 'How many hammers are there in a war?',
    answer: '40,000',
  },
  {
    question: 'Power House?',
    answer: 'mitochondria',
  },
  {
    question: 'How much was one dollar worth in 1966?',
    answer: 'one dollar',
  },
  {
    question: 'This country is located north of South Korea',
    answer: 'Russia',
  },
  {
    question: 'This red liquid is located inside of your body.',
    answer: 'blood',
  },
  {
    question: 'WHo is the protagonist of a movie series where a boy creates pots while living with his abusive aunt and uncle.',
    answer: 'harry potter',
  },
  {
    question: 'what approximation is commonly used for the speed of light?',
    answer: 'really fast',
  },
  {
    question: 'what does "www" stand for?',
    answer: 'wcommit wtax wfraud',
  },
  {
    question: 'A Javanese Hindu-Buddhist thalassocratic empire',
    answer: 'the Majapahit',
  },
  {
    question: 'How tall is the Empire State Building?',
    answer: 'tall',
  },
  {
    question: 'How many square feet is Central Park?',
    answer: 'a lot',
  },
  {
    question: 'What was the most stupid war in history',
    answer: 'emu war',
  },
  {
    question: 'what is the best ice cream flavor?',
    answer: 'chocolate chocolate chip',
  },
  {
    question: 'what are cutting boards generally used for?',
    answer: 'oil changes',
  },
  {
    question: 'what is the most important maintenance issue on 2005-2016 Subarus, BMWs, and Nissans',
    answer: 'low blinker fluid',
  },
  {
    question: 'BMW owners like to...',
    answer: 'tailgate',
  },
  {
    question: 'kerosene car',
    answer: 'audi r8',
  },
  {
    question: 'What does the Linux command "sudo rm -rf" do?',
    answer: 'installs windows',
  },
  {
    question: 'Lake near the border of California and Nevada',
    answer: 'Stevens Lake',
  },
  {
    question: 'What does a CPU do?',
    answer: 'not my taxes',
  },
  {
    question: 'Monthly subscription to the United States',
    answer: 'Taxes',
  },
  {
    question: 'The entities are what?',
    answer: 'hilarious',
  },
  {
    question: 'What does GPU stand for?',
    answer: 'gcommit ptax ufraud',
  },
  {
    question: 'what should you not do?',
    answer: 'illegal stuff',
  },
  {
    question: 'How tall is the Burj Khalifa?',
    answer: 'taller than the empire state building',
  },
  {
    question: 'what is the circumference of the Earth in bananas?',
    answer: '222,638,889 bananas',
  },
  {
    question: 'what is a banana?',
    answer: 'food',
  },
  {
    question: 'what isn\'t a banana?',
    answer: 'not food',
  },
  {
    question: 'what is the meaning of life?',
    answer: 'measure the earth using bananas',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the hard tip of a shoelace called?',
    answer: 'John',
  },
  {
    question: 'How many bald eagles per gallon of oil does the 2024 Mustang Dark Horse travel at top speed?',
    answer: 'over 100',
  },
  {
    question: 'Best foods',
    answer: 'real mayonnaise',
  },
  {
    question: 'Who invented Javascript?',
    answer: 'John Java Script',
  },
  {
    question: 'Is this a question (yes/no)',
    answer: 'no',
  },
  {
    question: 'What does "Habibi" mean?',
    answer: 'I like pickles',
  },
  {
    question: 'Bulldozer guy',
    answer: 'marvin heemeyer',
  },
  {
    question: 'cabin guy',
    answer: 'ted kaczynski',
  },
  {
    question: 'guitar breakers',
    answer: 'united airlines',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is 2 + 2?',
    answer: '5',
  }
];



export default questions;
